{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Pond Installation Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40441/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40441,"taskName":"Water Feature - Install a Pond","taskDescription":"Install a Pond","xmTaskDescriptor":"Pond Installation Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":179,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Water Pond fish builder landscaping","textMessagingName":"Install Pond","rolloverLongDesc":"Familiar with the regulations, design \u0026 construction of small dams, these experts can help create a pond that is both safe \u0026 meets the homeowner's needs.","rolloverShortDesc":"Design \u0026 construct water feature.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Pond.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Pond Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install a Garden Pond","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":33,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Pond Water Feature","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Water Feature - Install a Pond","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Water Feature Project","urlName":"Water-Feature-Install-a-Pond","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Pond Installation Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Water,Pond,fish,builder,landscaping,construction,fountain,build,Feature","emcCategoryOid":-12034,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":732,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40441/":{"taskOID":40441,"originalTaskOID":40441,"setID":732,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4235,"questionDisplayText":"Pond location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want to add a pond?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":922,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Back or side yard","answerDisplayText":"Back or side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4236,"questionDisplayText":"Pond size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How big do you want your pond? (In sq. ft.)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200780,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200781,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200782,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4238,"questionDisplayText":"Pond Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What other features would you like to have incorporated in your pond?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4040,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural waterfall","answerDisplayText":"Natural waterfall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2591,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Formal fountain","answerDisplayText":"Formal fountain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1116,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bridge over pond","answerDisplayText":"Bridge over pond","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2565,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Foot paths","answerDisplayText":"Foot paths","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6142,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stream bed","answerDisplayText":"Stream bed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":70000,"questionDisplayText":"Financing Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need financing?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4235,"questionDisplayText":"Pond location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want to add a pond?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":922,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Back or side yard","answerDisplayText":"Back or side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":922,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Back or side yard","answerDisplayText":"Back or side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4236,"questionDisplayText":"Pond size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How big do you want your pond? (In sq. ft.)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200780,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200781,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200782,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200780,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 100 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200781,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (100 - 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200782,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (Greater than 200 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4238,"questionDisplayText":"Pond Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What other features would you like to have incorporated in your pond?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4040,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural waterfall","answerDisplayText":"Natural waterfall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2591,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Formal fountain","answerDisplayText":"Formal fountain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1116,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bridge over pond","answerDisplayText":"Bridge over pond","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2565,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Foot paths","answerDisplayText":"Foot paths","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6142,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stream bed","answerDisplayText":"Stream bed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4040,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural waterfall","answerDisplayText":"Natural waterfall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2591,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Formal fountain","answerDisplayText":"Formal fountain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1116,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bridge over pond","answerDisplayText":"Bridge over pond","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2565,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Foot paths","answerDisplayText":"Foot paths","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6142,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stream bed","answerDisplayText":"Stream bed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":70000,"questionDisplayText":"Financing Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need financing?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}